Guide to the Solomon Feferman papers SC0907
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Solomon Feferman papers
1938-2016
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Feferman, Solomon.
SC0907
28.75 Linear Feet
The first series primarily document Feferman’s term as president of the Association for Symbolic Logic from 1980 to 1982. The material consists largely of correspondence, meeting agendas and minutes, and material from symposia and lectures. Accession 2018-045 largely consists of correspondence, publications and talks, Stanford University Mathematics Department material, and other professional material.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Solomon Feferman was a Professor of Mathematics and Philosophy and the Patrick Suppes Family Professor of Humanities and Sciences at Stanford University, he became Emeritus in 2004. Born December 13, 1928 in New York, New York, Feferman earned a B.S. from the California Institute of Technology in 1948, and his Ph.D. at University of California, Berkeley in 1957. His interests included mathematical logic, philosophy of mathematics, and history modern logic. Feferman died in 2016.
Description of the Collection
These papers primarily document Feferman’s term as president of the Association for Symbolic Logic from 1980 to 1982. The material consists largely of correspondence, meeting agendas and minutes, and material from symposia and lectures. Accession 2018-045 largely consists of correspondence, publications and talks, Stanford University Mathematics Department material, and other professional material.
Logic, Symbolic and Mathematical.; Association for Symbolic Logic.; Feferman, Solomon.; Feferman, Solomon.; Feferman, Solomon.; Stanford University. Department of Mathematics
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-227
  - Association for Symbolic Logic (ASL) Book Series Folder, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ASL Book Series Proposal (1 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ASL Book Series Proposal (2 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Book Series Extra Letters, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ASL Membership Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Journal of Symbolic Logic (JSL) Current, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agenda Work-Up & Memos from Mesiro, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ASL Book series-Boston, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AMS/ASL Translations Subcommittee, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ASL Meeting-Boston December 29, 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ASL: Editorial Board- Abstracts Format, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - European Committee for Logic, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ASL Prize & Awards, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Broadening-Letters to the Council, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Interned Polish Logicians, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposal: Latin American Symposium, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Broadening the ASL- Center Meeting; May 12, 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - IUHPS/DLMPS-Salzburg Meeting, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ASL (Active)-Pending, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Main Files, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ASL Publications Committee: Subcommittee I- New Journals, 1973- (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ASL-Bulletin of Information, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ASL-Bulletin of Information II, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ASL Council Minutes, 1983 January 7-8 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ASL-Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ASL,1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ruth Barcan Marcus-Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ASL New Business,1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NSF Travel Grant to Salzburg Meeting, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ASL-Final Work, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - ASL Correspondence (II), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ASL Correspondence (III), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ASL-Council Meeting, 1983 December 29-30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ASL-Meeting in Anaheim-Council Meeting Agenda, 1985 January (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ASL-Nominations, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2018-045
  - Publications Talks
    - Typical Ambiguity: Trying to have your cake and eat it too (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Typical Ambiguity (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Category Theory In Explicit Maths. "Collections approach" (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Prospectus Chapters 1, 2, 3 Vienna Talks Photos Tarnshi Potrait (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Lukasiewicz Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Tarshi-Some e-email responses (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Tarski: ABC Lists (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tarski Database (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Foundations of Explicit Maths. Chapters in papers, 211-212 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Foundations of Explicit Mathematics Chapters 8-10 Plus outlines Chapters 11-19 and end material, 212 Jul 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Foundations of Explicit Mathmatics Chapters 1-4, 6-7 and Suggestion revisions Chapters 1-4, 6-7, 212 Jun 13, 212 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Foundation of Explicit Mathematics Contents (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Computation and Recurrsion (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Notes for Chapter 2 "Fixing Frege" by John Bungers (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Preface / Papers (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Conviction and Caution-Responses (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Conviction and Caution-Original + Comments (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Tausshey-Todd / Meuger / Koehler (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Godel 1931C (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Type Symbols for YK 1931C (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Papers + Refs (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Godel-Life and Work-Responses (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Commentaries on my chapter Godel Life and Word (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Godel Life-Notes (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Godel Biography-Early Version (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Godel: Conviction and Caution [Final Version] + Bales, Gaudjean letter (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Proof Theory Symposium + "Some formal systems for the unlimted theory of structures and categories", 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - The explicit content of actual mathmatical analysis: formal systems of analysis and their interpretations (outline of proposed book), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Cleramont-Fernand Tutorials, 1994 Jul (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Logical Founds. Of Sci. Applic. Maths. (Transparencies) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Quine Memorial Symposium, 201 Jan 26 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Quine Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Lectures, Transparencies "Does Mathmatics Need New Axioms?" (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Logic Colloquium-Talk Transparencies "Functionary inductively presented topics", 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Tarski Conference Warsaw-Russel; Paradox Conference, Munnich, May 28-Jun 1, Jun 2-5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - UC Irvine Lecture: In the light of logic Godel and Tarski-Transparencies, 1999 Oct 19-22 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Hilbert's Program Symposium, 1985 Dec 29 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Austin Talk" Personal Shopping List for logical frameworks--tranparencies, 1993 Feb 5 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - UC Irvine visit, 1999 Oct 18-23 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - From Problem Driven Logic to Use Driven Logic (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Comments on Encylopedia Iraliara Article on Foundations of Programs (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - A Miscellany of Mathematical-Philosophical Quotations for Janet Lewis Winters 90th BIrthday, 1989 Aug 17 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - To a framework for polymorphinism-lecture transparencies, 1996 Nov-1987 Feb (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Browwer Meet, 1981 Jun 7-13 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - McCarthy Photos (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Meetups/People-Personal (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Metamath Lecture Notes 1-15, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Folder for Finished Notes: Metamath Course Lecture Notes 16-29, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Godel and 20th Century Logic-History of Science Lecture, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Inaugrual Lecture Stanford / Colloquim San Jose / "Deciding the undecided" Transparencies, 1994 Feb 13, 1994 Sep 22 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Ondimals-Notes and papers to take (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Conservation results for theories with choice and comprehension princniple (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Assorted Proof Theory Notes Atrp-higs (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Columbia Papers (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 291A (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "Some theories of strepth" Lecture-Patras Logic Colloquium, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Feferman ATR, 2017 Dec 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Lecture on Set Theory, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Set Theory Notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Set Theory Math 292B Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Set Theory Math 292A Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Phil 162 Philosophy of Mathematics (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Logic Societies Groups Newsletters, Info, Emails (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Book Shetehan for analysis misc. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Math 294 Section Notes (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - AC vs CA in Subsystems of Analysis (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Work. Founding Metamath (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Itenated ID and ID (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Kreisel (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Predicativity-Paper-more perspecous systems / Notes as ..., indepenent results (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Predicativity-Papers, Source, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Model Theory Notes (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 290A (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Applied Proof Theory 293A (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Notes on Proof Theory / Ondimal Notation For Munnich (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Predicative Syetems-Proofs of results (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Iremeted ID's (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Predecativity Re-Examined (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Handbook (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Use of Functional Models in Analysis / Impredicative Theorums (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Formal Systems of Analysis Seminar (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Topics in Proof Theory Godel's 2nd Then Reflection Principle, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Ontogeny and Philosophy of Axiom Systems-A structural conceptualist account (drafts) (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Philosophy of Mathematics-Drafts, comments (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Math-in-W? (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Light of Logic (Things to check) (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - In the light of logic, chapters in Prep [Old versions] + Outtakes (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Macmillan "Proof Theory Since 1960" Proof Sheets (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Proof Theory since 1960 (MacMillian Encyc) (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Bungers Encyc. Phil (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Fefernab-Hellman II (Challenges to Predicative Foundations of Arithemetic) Final Version, 1996 Jul 31 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Challenges to PFA / Fefferman Hellman II (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - A George Vellman / Hellman Feferman (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Professional
    - Sam Sebastian Meeting, 1990 Sep 25-29 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Aarhus Info / Copenhagen Map (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - BRICS Workshop PTAC, 1998 Aug 3-7 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Intuitions vs Monsters XX WCP Lecture Boston, 1998 Aug 11 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Kevin Stark Endangered Dreams / Scott Soaemen Understanding Truth, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Seuina Today (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Ah Chu! (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Current Travel Plans (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Logic Seminar "C++ Is Indefinite Math Logic Problem", 215 Nov 17 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Operational Set Theory WOLLIC Transpariencies, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Operational Theories of Sets (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - CST (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Constructive Theories of Functions and Classes (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Against Type Theory (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Berne Visist, 1997 Jun 16-23 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Ferferman-Jagen-Systems of EM with M/I (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Jagen-Seminar Notes on Universals in Explicit Maths. + Some of my notes (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Feferman, Jagen, Stahem-Book Plans-Foundation of Explicit Maths (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - ESSLIT Lectures Applicative Theories and Variable Types, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Lectures of ESSLLI Applicative Theories and Variable Types (AIX), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Mahlo Universes / Friendman Coquared (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Metamathematics Lecture Notes, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Lectures on … 293, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Reduction Workshops Munnich / "Does reductive proof theory have a variable rationale?", 1997 Sep 17 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Munnich Lecture Kurt Schutte's Way, 1999 Nov 5 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Reshiefed EM, Feferman-Jagen work (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Brono-KG Re Finitism, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Unfolding Refs / Finitism-Unfolding (with T. Staitham) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Prposal for a predicativity collection (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Predicativity: Problems and Prospects (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - History of Predicativity (With Mancosw) / For Dawson, Kawaniur, Van Daler volume (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Tanskue's Conception of Logic / Tarski Cemtenary (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Logical Form and Logical Constants UC Irvine (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Comments by Pratt Etch-Knath, Mitchell, Jeff Lellman, etc (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Hiutikke Papers (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Paris-Lecture, 1990 Mar 14 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Symposium on Synbolic Computation Engeler Meeting Zunich ETH, 1990 Mar 5-7 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Logic and Computation Conference Pittsburg, 1987 Jun 30-Jul 2 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Weye Vindicated "Das Kontinumen" / Florence talk: a modern developments of Weye foundational prgram" (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - La Rechenche Article (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - LICS: Santa Cruz, SF, and Monteral, Jun 22-25, Jun 20-23 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Paris Visit, 1992 Mar 15-Apr 13 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - One Hundred Years of Russel's Paradox, 201 Jun 2-5 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Will o the wisp Talk (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Tarshi Lectures I. Truth Unfounded, 206 Apr -3-7 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Open-Ended Schematic Ax. Systems ASL Lecture-Stanford (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Truth Unfounded Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Puflicatious Lists + Past lists (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Oslo Talk / Recurssion Theory and Set Theory: a marriage of conveniances / Notes to Grem.. Talk (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Turing Machines Lectures Notes and Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Tarski Lectures Lecture II: The "Logic" Question, 206 Apr 3-7 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Notes for Set Theory Ma 235 and additional Seminer Notes on Set Theory (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Papers of Godel Kleene Tarsk Seminars: Arith Classes Cylind. Algs (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Feferman Chapters III (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Chapters IV-I- (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter V-Larson (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Book Feferman (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fefernab Cgaoters I-1-I-55 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Chapters II Feferman Math, Dept (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Chapters II Feferman Math, Dept (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tait Misc (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - S.F 1st Class (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Refile-School (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Itenated ID and FP Theories (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Tucker Zucker (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Feferman Metamath SSO-15, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Course Notes Generalization of Recurion Theory, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Metamath Notes SS 16-29, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Recursion Theory / Jyvaskala meet / Oxford meet, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Meetings Past (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Msothes (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Enc. Britannica Article / Dubueatents (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Logic DIV (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kreisel-Howard BI + TI + Continuity / Booh Publ (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Visits (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Tarsku meeting / Tarski Symposium, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Annual Faculty Report, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Salary Stuff w/Rosse-Spring, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Schutte (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Meetings (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Misc Feferman (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Phil Dept., 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Currents (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Today / Current Spring-Dec, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Today (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Now!, 1998-Spring 1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Project Description Copies (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Vaught Memorial, 2002 Jun 2 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Turning Works (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - In the Light of Logic, Reviews + Connections (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - CV Publications Bio (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Feferman CV Bio (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Tarski Questionnaires Interviews File, etc (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Tarski Interludes-Early Version / Interlude, 1924: Banach-Tarski / Interlude 1946: Tarski's Princeton Lecture, 1924 / 1946 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Chapters-Paper Transparencies, 2012 Oct 11 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Old Chapters 7-9 / Tarski Ch 10+ / Tarski's 60s (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Cal Tech Meetings Abstracts, 1996 Nov 15-17 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - When Tarski Met Godel / History Session AMS Meet. Caltech, 1996 Nov 16-17 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Alfred Tarski ad a watershed Meeting in Logic + Tarski and CS (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - References (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - History of The Logic Position Stanford Math Dept. (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - ASL (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Aachem Talk, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Paris Talk / M. Logic Seminar, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - NSF Proposal, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - NSF Proposal References / Krisel papers (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Letter from Anthony Will (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Letter from Jaroslaw Kozak (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Recent and Not So Recent (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hauser, Arana, Schimanovich (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Reactions to Rome Paper: Quine, Friedman (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Bibliopolis, Del Franci, Klauspefers (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - GK-Delgell Correspond (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Kreisel-AM Review (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - H.F-G.K-MB Affair (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Selected Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Letters from GH, 1982 Jan 1 / Jul 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Courses, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - M. Yaten in Turning Volume (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Rec'd May 19, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 0, 2017 Apr 20 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Copeland-Proudloof (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Letter from Jalen(?) (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Manders: What numbers are real? (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, Aut 1989-Winter 1990 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Rec'd, 1990 Apr-May (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Things to Do / Mailings, Summer 1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Things to Do, 1990 Autumn (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Today's Mail, 1990 Summer-Autumn (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Current! Correspondence, 1981 Jan-Nov (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Things To Do (Lists) (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Current / Priscilla-Action (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Assorted (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Action / General Correspondence, 1988 Sep (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Action (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Priscilla-Do (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1998 Mar-Nov (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Current (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - SHC (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Current, Early 1989 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Emails, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Aczel / Martin-Lof Theories with one Universe, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Strahm-Unfolding NFA Draft II, 1997 Jul (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - French Correspondence de Rouillam / Sinaceur / Imbert (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Intentional Directory of Logicians Entry (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Harvey Friedman 60th B'day Conference Ohio State, 209 May 14-17 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Part Three On Turning / 9. Turning's "Oracle": From Absolute to Relative Computability-and Back / 10. Turning in the Land of O(z) (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Metapredicativity Seminar / Background Notes, 2010 Autumn (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Innovational in the Humanities Proposal (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Taski for Encyclopedia of Philosophy (Supplement) (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Logic Seminar, 2012-2013 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Peter Koellner EFI Project Howard / My paper, Koellnen: critique / Comments for Workshop, 2011-2012 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - OSC + Math Practice Axs (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - OST, etc (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Language and Axioms for Constructive and Definable Mathematics Proofs of Trials (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Elephant Feferman 20 Copes / Jan Stone / Faillace / S.F. Book (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Carnap on Explicit Maths (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Feferman Aczel / Lewr MS + Two Patters to Sief (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Beeson (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Constructive Theories of Functions and Classes (Mons Paper) / Some papers on Constrcitionalists (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Beeson (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Kreisel: Thinking About Man: Handware, Software, Wet Ware, 1984 Apr 13 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Replete Furs, Furs (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Natural W.O.S / Nayhabet (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Notes on Ordinals (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bachmawn-Isles Systems (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Levitz (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Ordinals (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Kreisel Alarallel between Wittgenstein's ways and works, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Schutte Fest-75th B'day, 1984 Jun 22-23 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Lecture Notes ID Project (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mons Lectures-Notes, etc (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Constructivity Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Martin-Lof Jewell (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Beeson-Correspodence (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Notes on the Formalization of Bishop's Constructive Maths (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Proof Theory Course 293A+293B Lectures on Constructivists, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Math 292B Constructivity in Algebra (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Constructive and Effective Algebra (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Phil Dept, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Tarski Book (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Backup Failed, 2014 Dec 16 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Journals + Calendars (Box 14)
    - NSF Grants, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Recursive Progressions Contract4 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - NSF (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - NSF (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - NSF, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - List of Meetings Attended 1957- Travels (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Now! (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Now-Jun 203, 2003 Jun (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Very Current 201-202 Today, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Schock Pringe (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Godel's Theorenm Nubds abd Nacgubes / UCB Sorubg 203 / Part II / Grades, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - U.C. Berkeley Spring 203 Visit Forms, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Schock Pringe Events/Info / OSLO Oct. 19-25 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Schock Lecture (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Logic Methodology Group U.C. Gustory of -- + Students, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Report, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Polish Philosophers (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Tarski-Misc (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Anita-Warsaw LICS Talk, 1997 Jun 29 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Templeton Foundation (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Templeton Proposal, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Templeton Proposal (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Computation and Recurrsion Theses (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Templeton Foundation Grant 21231 Reports, 2011-2013 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Predicativity (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Notes and Letters (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - LMH Proposal, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - The nature and significance of Godel's incompleteness Theorems / IAS, Princeton, 2006 Nov 17 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Reviews of AT: L (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Lecture Transparencies / Talk / Moscow Conference + "Hyman meets Kleene", 1978 Aug 17-22 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Systems of Ordinal Rep/ For Metapredicativity, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - CST (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Godel Symposi, Salybeng + Acad. Sei. Symp. (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Mints Obit, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Girand / Jewell (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Type-Free Papers (Box 16, Folder 36)